import React from 'react'

let fruitsAndVeggies = {
    title: "Fruits and Veggies",
    questions: [
        {   
            question: "The Arthur Turner plant produces this kind of fruit",
            answers: ["Peach", "Pear", "Apple", "Plum"],
            correct: "Apple"
        },
        {   
            question: "This well-known cucumber is known as the King of the ______",
            answers: ["Ridge", "Garden", "Ring", "Rim"],
            correct: "Ridge"
        },
        {   
            question: "Kiwifruit is otherwise known as this",
            answers: ["Japanese Plum", "Asian Pear", "Indian Fig", "Chinese Gooseberry"],
            correct: "Chinese Gooseberry"
        },
        {   
            question: "Broccoli originated on this continent",
            answers: ["Africa", "South America", "Asia", "Europe"],
            correct: "Europe"
        },
        {   
            question: "Ribes Grossularia is the latin name for this berry",
            answers: ["Blackberry", "Elderberry", "Gooseberry", "Raspberry"],
            correct: "Gooseberry"
        },
        {   
            question: "The dish Bubble and Squeak is potatoes combined with this",
            answers: ["Peas", "Brussel Sprouts", "Turnip", "Carrot"],
            correct: "Brussel Sprouts"
        },
        {   
            question: "This percentage of a cucumber is water",
            answers: ["5", "30", "40", "90"],
            correct: "90"
        },
        {   
            question: "This vitamin is most prevalent in a lime",
            answers: ["C", "D", "E", "A"],
            correct: "C"
        },
        {   
            question: "Strawberries belong to this family of plants",
            answers: ["Nightshade", "Grass", "Mallow", "Rose"],
            correct: "Rose"
        },
        {   
            question: "This fruit may also be known as a plantain",
            answers: ["Damson", "Dates", "Persimmon", "Banana"],
            correct: "Banana"
        },
        {   
            question: "Which of the following is NOT a type of grape",
            answers: ["Zinfandel", "Chardonnay", "Avon", "Ugni Blanc"],
            correct: "Avon"
        },
        {   
            question: "This vegetable often gets confused with the sweet potato",
            answers: ["Watermelon", "Ugli Fruit", "Watercress", "Yam"],
            correct: "Yam"
        },
        {   
            question: "This is the correct name of a type of peach",
            answers: ["Ilberta", "Elberta", "Alberta", "Ulberta"],
            correct: "Elberta"
        },
        {   
            question: "This fruit grows in bunches known as hands",
            answers: ["Pear", "Kiwi", "Apple", "Banana"],
            correct: "Banana"
        },
        {   
            question: "Washington, Victoria, Santa Rosa, and Bokhara are varieties of this vegetable",
            answers: ["Carrot", "Parsnip", "Turnip", "Potato"],
            correct: "Potato"
        },
        {   
            question: "There are roughly this many varieties of avocados",
            answers: ["500", "5000", "5", "50"],
            correct: "500"
        },
        {   
            question: "This Spanish city is also the name of a type of orange",
            answers: ["Madrid", "Valencia", "Barcelona", "Seville"],
            correct: "Seville"
        },
        {   
            question: "This fruit has the varieties Kara, Dancy, Fremont, Iyo, Honey, and Ponkan",
            answers: ["Lime", "Lemon", "Mandarin", "Mango"],
            correct: "Mandarin"
        },
        {   
            question: "This name comes before Lear when talking about cranberries",
            answers: ["Edward", "Ben", "Daniel", "David"],
            correct: "Ben"
        },{   
            question: "This fruit is often called the World's Smelliest Fruit",
            answers: ["Ugli Fruit", "Banana", "Lemon", "Durian"],
            correct: "Durian"
        }
    ]
}

export default fruitsAndVeggies